{
	"projectName": "StudyName",
	"initialScore": 1000,
	"shuffleScenarioOrder": false,
	"users": [
		{"name": "1", "identifier": "1", "password": "1"},
		{"name": "2", "identifier": "2", "password": "2"},
		{"name": "3", "identifier": "3", "password": "3"},
		{"name": "4", "identifier": "4", "password": "4"},
		{"name": "5", "identifier": "5", "password": "5"}
	],
	"scenarios": [
		{
			"scenarioName": "A",
			"description": "This scenario is structured, low uncertainty. Connections are set, and topics are shown.",
			"showTopics": true,
			"connections": [
				["1", "3"],
				["4", "5"]
			],
			"timeout": 18000,
			"questions": [
				{
					"question" : "Name 3 African mammals",
					"answers" : ["Lion", "Cheetah", "Monkey"],
					"topic": "Animals"
				},
				{
					"question": "Name 3 brands of cars",
					"answers": ["Lexus", "BMW", "Nissan"],
					"topic": "Cars"
				},
				{
					"question": "Name 3 programming languages",
					"answers": ["C++", "Python", "Java"],
					"topic": "Computers"
				}
			],
			"answersPerUser": 3
		},
		{
			"scenarioName": "B",
			"description": "This scenario is structured, high uncertainty. Connections are set, but topics are hidden",
			"showTopics": false,
			"connections": [
				["1", "3"],
				["4", "5"]
			],
			"timeout": 1800,
			"questions": [
				{
					"question" : "Name 3 African mammals",
					"answers" : ["Lion", "Cheetah", "Monkey"]
				},
				{
					"question": "Name 3 brands of cars",
					"answers": ["Lexus", "BMW", "Nissan"]
				},
				{
					"question": "Name 3 programming languages",
					"answers": ["C++", "Python", "Java"]
				}
			],
			"answersPerUser": 3
		},
		{
			"scenarioName": "C",
			"description": "This scenario is non-structured, low uncertainty. Connections are not set, but topics are shown",
			"showTopics": true,
			"connections": [],
			"timeout": 1800,
			"questions": [
				{
					"question" : "Name 3 African mammals",
					"answers" : ["Lion", "Cheetah", "Monkey"],
					"topic": "Animals"
				},
				{
					"question": "Name 3 brands of cars",
					"answers": ["Lexus", "BMW", "Nissan"],
					"topic": "Cars"
				},
				{
					"question": "Name 3 programming languages",
					"answers": ["C++", "Python", "Java"],
					"topic": "Computers"
				}
			],
			"answersPerUser": 3
		},
		{
			"scenarioName": "D",
			"description": "This scenario is non-structured, high uncertainty. No connections and topics are hidden.",
			"showTopics": false,
			"connections": [],
			"timeout": 1800,
			"questions": [
				{
					"question" : "Name 3 African mammals",
					"answers" : ["Lion", "Cheetah", "Harambe"]
				},
				{
					"question": "Name 3 brands of cars",
					"answers": ["Lexus", "BMW", "Nissan"]
				},
				{
					"question": "Name 3 programming languages",
					"answers": ["C++", "Python", "Java"]
				}
			],
			"answersPerUser": 3
		}
	]
}